GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
Why did you save me?
I would have left me to die, why did you save me?
and made him disabled?
For what?
Hasn't changed at all.
What's happened?
You have a stroller...
...broken?
What? Yes, yes.
So...
...don't remember.
I see they are frozen.
Thank you.
Why are you crying?
I didn't cry.
To be honest, I'm your, your, your fan.
Thank you.
Just for everything, thank you for everything.
For the fact that you exist in the world.
Me too.
I'm grateful too.
Will you get home?
I...
You...
...give me a ride?
- What?
- You are my fan...
I won't leave you.
A friend came to pick me up.
What? What's going on here?
My God!
- God, Sol!
- Thank you for everything.
Take it.
Wait a second.
I don't have any gifts...
but you love it.
Hold it.
Help yourself. Goodbye!
SERIES 4
Have you come to your senses yet?
What am I doing here?
You have lost consciousness.
Wait a little, the doctor will come
and will examine you.
What year is it now?
What?
2023rd.
KOREA UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Song Jae...
My son...
My Sung Jae!
Only loved ones can come here. Sorry.
Yes, I understand.
My Sung Jae...
My son...
CEO Kim, say something!
CEO Kim, a few words!
Are you Lim Sol?
This was found on Ryu Sung Jae.
Look.
How? How?
Where...
It wasn't a dream.
Baek In Hyuk immediately recognized you from the photo
and told us.
He said you and Ryu Sung Jae know each other.
The future has changed!
You didn't notice anything strange
in his behavior?
You were the last person he saw yesterday
before death.
I can save him.
We need to go back.
Well why doesn't it work?
Why, why?
The first news of the new year.
Tragically passed away last night
Ryu Sung Jae.
As it turned out, during his lifetime the late singer
suffered from depression and insomnia.
This is a big blow for the fans.
Sun Jae had a hard time due to rumors
and negative comments.
If I remembered you yesterday...
Then...
I would hug you and never let you go.
Take it.
I wouldn't leave you alone.
Hello?
This is Baek In Hyuk.
You saw each other yesterday.
How is Song Jae? Did you look too bad?
I didn’t even think that he was tired of living.
Did you know?
Knew he felt guilty
in front of you?
- What?
- You should know...
What are you talking about?
Why Sung Jae...
Baek In Hyuk?
The subscriber is temporarily unable to
receive calls.
Leave a message...
So they only glow at midnight?
Then maybe...
- Get out!
- Get out, evil spirit, from the body of my daughter!
Spare my Salt, ancestors.
- Have mercy.
- Spare my Salt, ancestors. Have mercy.
Back?
Yes, she's back!
I'm back!
But where?
In 2008?
You kept hiding and hiding,
and now it’s finally out?
- Shameless!
- What?
- Please...
How dare you inhabit other people's bodies!
Come out immediately!
- Hurt! Stop it! Mother!
- Get out, get out!
- What's wrong with you?
There is no spirit!
I didn’t believe in this.
Where are you going in the middle of the ritual?
What other ritual, mom?
You yourself said that you
some spirit has taken over
and you don't remember anything.
That's why we called the shaman!
I asked for a ritual
and now you're trying to sneak away, right?
I?
Help me please.
18 YEARS OLD
It seems that an evil spirit has possessed me.
I see. I see a lot of spirits.
Many, many spirits of young girls,
that is constantly being sucked out
life from your body!
How brave I am.
Salt.
Just don't say that you're completely
you don't remember anything.
I remembered. I remembered everything.
I studied so much that my head
went around.
Seriously? How good.
That's it, mom, that's it.
- What kind of business is this?
- God.
Song Jae...
Move away!
-Where are you going?
- He also steps over the altar.
Lim Sol!
Song Jae...
Let's talk.
I have a boyfriend.
18 YEARS OLD
Maybe you can let me pass?
I'll be quick.
Pervert, I told you no!
I'm crazy.
What have you done, Sol?
How much time has passed?
A whole 10 days?
Yes. This is not time, but chance.
A chance to go back in time.
If I go back later,
is there another attempt left?
I lasted two months.
What will happen this time?
Yes.
I can change everything.
We have to try.
Song Jae!
Stop!
Have you taken off the bandage? How's the shoulder? Doesn't it hurt?
Look what I brought you. Take it.
That's right, the package is heavy.
There are books and jars here. Maybe they will come in handy.
Banks, by the way, help to recover
after surgery.
You can put them at home so you don't have to go
to the hospital every time.
Like this.
What is this?
- This...
- What's wrong with you?
Are you angry?
Sorry.
I'll explain everything!
It wasn't me who called you a pervert.
- What?
- This is 18-year-old Sol.
- She's just stupid.
-Who are you then?
I am Salt from the distant future!
Look, it's a time machine.
Your watch took me back to the past
so that you survive!
Are you going crazy?
Will he believe it?
The spirit took over me.
- This spirit again?
- It's true, Sung Jae.
Did you see what happened yesterday?
Here. Look.
- What are you doing?
- Now...
Here. Talisman against evil spirits.
You still don't believe me?
I didn’t understand anything then
and didn’t recognize any of my friends.
So the spirit found the guy?
What?
This is the spirit of a young girl! Song Jae!
Everything is fine?
Let's meet.
18 YEARS OLD
I want.
You...
You! You!
What, did you hit yourself?
Let's go.
Don't look.
- Leave me alone!
- What?
"To be your girlfriend -
It's a dream, really!
Tick ​​tock, lunch time!
It's time to eat deliciously.
Ding-ding! Alarm clock Sol is ringing.
Get up quickly!"
What? Ding... Ding-ding?
What a nightmare.
Yes. Choose.
The first is my healing hands. Second...
Third, shut your mouth.
I can do it myself. Give it here.
No need.
What about the second option?
Oh you! So you made Sol fall in love with you?
So, is our granny back again?
How... How did you understand?
Yesterday you were different.
By the way.
Where are the hearts?
Do you like Salt?
Of course I like it.
- It's not true!
- What should I do?
There is you here.
Third, third!
It would be better to remain silent.
That's it.
No relationship.
I would never agree!
Some spirit has taken possession of you,
and you don't remember anything.
That's why we called the shaman!
Can I do whatever I want?
Will I be back soon?
I... This... I wanted to ask you.
Do you happen to know where Sol lives?
I want to give her something back.
This is my saucepan.
And Sol is my daughter.
She came to see you
I treated myself to chicken soup in this pan.
But that was a long time ago
are you just returning it now?
What? Is this her daughter?
- Strange grandfather.
- Things were going on, it slipped my mind.
Sorry.
Here, take this, I washed it.
Fine.
Goodbye.
Wait!
You only paid 11 dollars.
Oh... Oh... What are you talking about?
I called you and asked you to return the tape,
and you detained her for a couple of days.
That's two more dollars!
I don't understand what you're talking about at all.
My God! Are you stuck?
Yes!
So please, one more time.
Camera.
Motor!
So you are a dentist.
Have you recently opened your own clinic?
Come visit us sometime.
I'll clean you up.
- Wait, stop.
- Let's stop!
Okay, very good. But a little more cunning.
- Take a sip of coffee.
- Yes.
And smile wider.
Smile. Fine?
Smile, yes.
- Fine.
- Motor!
So you are a dentist.
Have you recently opened your own clinic?
Come visit us sometime.
I'll clean you up.
- What?
- Where did the tooth go?
Cut!
Have you seen the dentist
without a front tooth?
Replace!
Now!
I'll put it back in now!
- Let's go.
- Can we do it again...
- Let's go already.
- Wait.
Take him away!
Give me a tooth!
Go crazy.
One new tooth won't save you!
Seriously...
What should I do?
I can't even go to the toilet.
Damn constipation.
Everything is the same.
Did you come to see Tae-sung?
No. To you.
For what?
Did you know?
Knew he felt guilty
in front of you?
What?
You should know...
What should I know?
In Hyuk. What did you want to tell me?
What? What are you watching?
In Hyuk. If you want
say something, say something.
God... What if I don’t want to?
Maybe you want to tell me something
in 2023?
Then don't be shy and call right away.
That's it, I remembered.
Don't run after Sun Jae anymore.
Exactly, Sung Jae!
When you go to the audition,
don't take it.
So that his feet are in that hall
there wasn't, got it?
What do you care about Sun Jae and me?
In Hyuk. Think about it.
If you come to the audition
with a handsome guy like Sung Jae
They will take him, not you.
Do you know why?
Producers are looking for diamonds in the rough
not roadside stones.
- By the way...
- Got it?
In terms of? I'm a stone and Sun Jae is a diamond?
Doesn't matter. If you want to protect your friend...
and live in peace, do not forget my words.
I really wish him the best.
Bye!
Stop!
Don't run after Sung Jae!
Long time no see, Sung Jae.
Wow. Did you receive the certificate?
I'm jealous.
We should celebrate this.
- I'm in a hurry.
- Study?
Certainly. The road to sailing is closed,
look for another one.
Fuck off.
I'm just sorry for you, buddy.
But I warned you.
I should have listened.
Stop overacting, Sung Jae.
Don't tense your shoulders so much.
We need to be more modest.
Life punishes for greed.
Hurt?
You too...
don't relax.
Suddenly you weaken, you don’t push off like that,
and one day
you will stretch your muscles.
Like me.
- Hello, Sung Jae!
- Stop!
I think you were telling me
what your mother dreamed about.
So that you get into the Korean team.
Better go ask for forgiveness at her grave,
don't give it to me
Idiot advice, you freak!
Dog. I'll tell you now...
Song Jae! Song Jae! Song Jae!
Wait, no need.
Hey, hey, Sung Jae, don't.
Let him go, let him go.
Sun Jae, stop it! Enough, no need.
Everything is fine, everything is fine.
-Where are you going? Come on, hit me! Let's!
- No!
Stand!
Why are you touching mom?
Nothing to say - keep quiet.
What a man!
Come on, come on.
Yes! It was you who wanted to steal the swimming trunks
in the pool.
I shouldn’t have let you go then!
This is blood... Tired of living?
Should I bring you to your senses?
If you come again
deal with Sung Jae,
there will be problems.
- Crap.
- Hush, hush.
So. What's that noise?
Are you a chicken? It's over for you.
Come... Come here. Go...
What a shameless one!
Come here! Where did you run?
Stand!
We never talked.
- Let's go.
- Hurt. Let me in!
Salt. Why did you contact
with such an idiot?
Because of you I am embarrassed now!
Gorgeous. Let me go, let's talk.
I warned you.
Don't you really understand?
But it wasn’t in a good way.
You're just swearing.
- Shut your mouth.
- What did you say?
She's funny.
Do you like Daesung?
I'll leave him today. Is it coming?
Let me go and we'll talk everything over.
And how can I trust you?
You just recently said
that you will never part.
Last chance.
If you let me go before three, I will forgive you.
Who are you, friend?
One, two, three!
Mop!
Is it possible to humiliate yourself like that because of a guy?
- Hey!
- So disgusting!
- Let her go, let her go!
- Let go! Let me go!
Girls!
Are you fighting?
We play, we just play.
- It's a joke.
- Yes, as a joke.
Is it true?
Don't quarrel!
Hooligans.
I saw him somewhere.
CEO Kim!
CEO?
- What is he doing here?
- What's wrong with her?
-Where are you going?
- Where?
Let me go! I'll leave him. Move away already!
Damn, it hurts like that. Crap.
Here.
You will call.
Has she come again?
Come in.
Song Jae!
Sun Jae had a hard time due to rumors
and negative comments.
Hello.
GYMA VIDEO AND DVD
Lord. Like two peas in a pod.
Hello. Did something happen?
Is Sun Jae home?
No, he left recently.
He changed his clothes and went to the hospital
for treatment.
Which hospital?
Wait.
Has he changed his clothes?
I wanted to tell him something.
- Shall I wait in the room?
- He’s not at home, why?
Let's. I'll pass.
Maybe I should drop off the package now?
No, you can't do that. To the guy's room?
If you want, you can give it to me when we meet.
Stomach...
Can I go to the toilet?
You go home. The house is right under your nose.
By the way, I would like it myself.
And quickly.
Stomach. Stomach! Stomach! Faster! Faster!
My stomach... Faster...
As a result, I snuck into someone else's house.
Is Sung Jae's room upstairs?
Crap!
Lee Byung Hun married Lee Min Jung!
Won Bin is married to Lee Na Young!
Rain is married to Kim Tae Hee!
What is this superpower?
Wow!
Here.
JN ENTERTAINMENT
God!
Hyun Bin married Son Ye Jin!
The smell here is, of course, strong.
They asked me to pass it on.
Certificate for outstanding athletes.
True, it arrived late.
CREDIT
And I'll be there.
So that you don't feel lonely,
so that you don't think about bad things.
Funny.
My God. It's already summer and I'm
I've never worn it yet.
We need to fix it.
Hello. Finished?
- Yes.
- Why so sweaty?
I ran around a bit.
OK.
Alcohol can't save me anymore, but he...
Probably overheated. I'm imagining it.
What?
Is she in my room?
Salt.
Get up.
Salt. Get up, I say.
Go crazy.
Overheated?
Sound asleep.
Crap.
- Hello?
- Tae Son! I missed you!
Funny?
All!
Taesung, why are you staring at the phone?
She constantly called me...
and suddenly stopped?
Yes? You broke up.
You said she was kind of strange.
And so it was.
- But I changed my mind.
- In terms of?
Are you tired of Ga Hyun
and started dating her.
- I don’t know.
- Jerk.
Sorry.
I'm already leaving.
Dad is there, how will you leave?
Through the window.
- I'll tie the rope...
- Don't come closer!
Sit there.
Don't come near.
The news will end, then you will leave.
Fine.
Maybe you can explain all this?
I...
- ...I wanted to convey...
- Package.
Why were you sleeping on the floor?
So, I didn't sleep.
Do you think I'll believe it?
Don't believe it, but it's true.
Again, you may not believe it, but I'm honest.
and a decent person, it's true!
Just next to you...
I'm weird.
Exactly.
Why are you weird with me?
But you can't...
forget about it?
Salt.
You...
I like you.
Have you forgotten everything that happened?
In the pool!
Was it in the pool?
Come on. And what will happen to me from this?
I'm not drunk, honestly.
Are you still angry since then?
Maybe this is nothing to you.
But for me - no!
Sorry, Sung Jae.
Forget.
Did I get very drunk that day?
Strongly? How's the pig?
To be honest, I don't remember anything.
What?
Sorry.
I get drunk very quickly.
That is...
you got drunk and don't remember anything?
Cold.
At least something good.
That's good!
In general, first the tincture
drank so easily
and then suddenly I...
At least keep quiet.
I put on such a performance
but she doesn't remember.
When you can't sleep...
you can read these books.
For what?
Do you think my life is hard?
We all have moments like this.
It seems...
that the whole world has turned against you.
Will you put me on my feet?
I would be delighted!
Thank you...
that you live.
But they once told me:
“The weather is good, so move on with your life.
If it rains, wait it out
and move on with your life."
And maybe someday...
it will become much easier for you.
Therefore, Sung Jae...
if you want to die...
wait another day.
For me to come back...
and saved you.
Let's be friends again.
If you don't want...
just don't push me away...
me so quickly.
She doesn't even know.
He said don't come near.
Yes, just...
A fly was flying above you.
It won't work.
Are you burning your blanket?
Let's be friends?
How can we be friends?
- We can...
- I'm not friends with girls!
There is no such friendship!
Did I ask for support? Was there such a thing?
When I see you I feel
weak and defenseless!
I'm disgusted!
Let's pretend we don't know each other.
What should I do, Sung Jae?
I can only try to support you!
Go and buy different books,
which you won't even read.
That's it!
I'm finally walking, but I have
hands tied and mouth closed.
I'm already suffocating! I feel bad too!
Exactly.
You won't give me what I want.
Therefore...
don't suffer...
and don't try to make friends with me.
Leave.
Here. Leave.
Go away, who am I telling!
Crap.
Did I ask for support? Was there such a thing?
When I see you I feel
weak and defenseless!
I'm disgusted!
Therefore...
don't try to be friends with me.
Leave.
My God.
What to do?
Crap. My body seems to
works the same.
When necessary - no,
when it is not necessary - please.
Come already! God!
Hyun Joo! Gotcha.
Why don't you answer?
Where are you going, where are you going?
What should I do with my tooth?
I have already agreed with my uncle.
Wait, wait, wait.
What kind of clinic does he have?
It will be faster to be reborn already!
Saturday, are you happy?
Stand! Because of this tooth I lost
life-changing opportunity.
Compensate! Compensate!
Cleaning.
- For free!
- Stop!
Can I also get whitening as a gift?
Crap. Why is it closed here too?
Yes, you're great.
Wow. Here comes Hyun Joo.
What's wrong with you?
No! Don't come near!
I really wanted to fly
and celebrate with you.
Sorry.
Happy birthday.
I miss you, son.
I thought you'd dress up since you're late.
Didn't meet your expectations?
Tell the truth.
Are you upset?
Personality disorder.
Yes. You guessed it right.
I'll explain everything, listen.
There is a young, naive Sol
and adult, confident Sol.
- Yes?
- This is for me as an adult
I don't like that young Sol
meets with you.
I'm a graduate, but I run after guys.
Should you worry?
Schoolgirl in love with me Sol
and adult careerist Sol
are they fighting inside you?
So you're smart. Yes, things like that.
- Who won?
- I won.
Well done.
Therefore...
let's break up.
She herself said that it should be noted.
- What's happened?
- What? Mark?
18 YEARS OLD
- No!
- What?
No, no, no, no... No.
No.
No no. I'm telling you, no!
That's it, that's it, don't!
For one of the guests
We have prepared a surprise.
Attention.
- Let's go.
- It's a surprise. Wait.
I'll treat you, let's get out of here!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
I DON'T LIKE RAIN, KON YU AND KANG DONG WON
Don't look. Don't look!
I DON'T LIKE SO JI SOP
DON'T LIKE JO IN SON
Is that you? Hit the target straight.
AND PRINCE TAE SON - YES!
FOR SUCH A COOL GUY I AM THE BEST MATCH
I LIKE DAE SON!
I LIKE EVERYTHING ABOUT TE SONA!
I LIKE IT MOST EVERYTHING IN THE WORLD
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO IMAGINE
A WORLD WITHOUT TAESON
DAE SON IS THE BEST. HURRAY, TAE SON!
Taesung, happy birthday!
What have you been doing in the last year?
stupid?
Blow it out.
- Congratulations!
Tell the truth.
Didn't you remember about the surprise?
Maybe. Apparently so.
I didn't know you liked me so much.
That's it? I didn't know myself!
What? Are you ashamed now?
Shall we go eat?
Did you eat miyeokguk today?
Miyeokguk?
Does dad remember what is today?
Seriously?
Poor me.
Yes?
Two servings of soup.
Fine.
Why don't you eat?
You're the first one on my birthday
took me to a diner.
Miyeokguk is prepared everywhere, did you know?
Come on, eat already and grow up.
Be smart.
Tasty?
Don’t they usually bring it with soup?
more different snacks?
What's happened?
Fell in love again?
I'm trying to understand...
what young Sol could find
in an ordinary school student like you.
Are your feelings gone?
OK. If this Salt returns,
don't hurt her.
Don't hurt her.
Meet like schoolchildren!
Go to libraries
to bookstores...
- More?
- Don’t get on a motorcycle, it’s dangerous.
Don't go out late.
- More?
- And touching her...
- Is it possible?
- I mean, is it possible?
Brats.
What else! It is forbidden!
God. She is me, and I am she.
What kind of nonsense am I talking about?
So he went to the agency.
Has the sailor left the water?
- What?
- Look.
Is this Ryu Sung Jae?
He won't become a star.
Baek In Hyuk at the audition.
Where is it?
-Have you passed?
- What?
Why did he take Sung Jae with him?
I told you to keep his feet in the hall...
What are you talking about?
- Sun Jae went to help his father.
- What?
Are you going?
How good.
Don't meddle in his business.
You're with Tae-sung
Is Sun Jae a joke to you?
What?
What nonsense?
Salt! How are you?
- Please.
- Bring us water!
Sun Jae, water!
Table 10!
- Hello?
-Are you still in the cafe?
- Yes. I'm busy.
-Did you tell Lim Sol everything?
Are you communicating?
- What?
- She was looking for you!
She ran as if they were chasing her,
then she fell down the stairs.
I asked how she was
and there’s already no trace of her.
Water please!
Just a second, excuse me.
Listen, I'm busy.
I'm not interested. Bye.
Song Jae!
I'll change it now.
She was looking for you!
She ran as if they were chasing her,
then she fell down the stairs.
I asked how she was
and there’s already no trace of her.
Sorry...
Our meat is about to burn.
Son! Where are you going?
Lim Sol. Lim Sol!
Where am I?
What's the next stop?
It will be the last one.
Come on. I probably fell asleep.
Is it true?
Go crazy.
JUYANG RESERVOIR
FISHING IS PROHIBITED
I've been here before.
I'll cross the road.
JUYAN-RI, 1
Oh my God.
Girl.
Are you studying at school?
Good evening.
God.
Wait. Stop. Wait.
Don't run away! Wait!
Wait, I'm not a bad person!
Why are you running away? My God.
- Leave me alone!
- I'm not bad, girl!
- Wait. Wait!
- What's wrong with you?
I'm generally harmless.
Don't come near! I'll call the police!
Will you call? What? Why call?
I won't do anything to you.
- Let me in!
- Honestly, you don’t need to call anyone!
No need!
Here! Stop here!
- Let me in!
- I'm not a bad person, really!
Wait, I'll explain everything to you now.
No need to call!
Salt. Lim Sol!
Crap!
After the accident, someone saved me.
Do you remember his name?
Everything is fine?
What's happened?
Did you hurt yourself? No? Let me see.
Leave.
Leave!
Why did you save me?
I would have left me to die, why did you save me?
and made him disabled?
For what?
I lost...
memories...
or...
...you?
Doesn't it hurt? Scared?
Let's go to the hospital.
So, after In Hyuk we have...
Song Jae! Will you try it?
Well... Let's go.
- Hello?
- What?
Hello...
My name is Ryu Sung Jae.
And what?
Do you know me?
Don't know.
Salt...
GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
Don't miss this moment for anything.
- Salt!
- You saved me.
- Forty will not remain in debt.
- Martin.
He started dating Lim Seol
just like that.
- At least pretend.
- And we don’t even know each other.
I think he looks great!
Today you are nasty!
What? Attention!
- Exactly then?
- We can change your destiny.
I won't have any regrets. Everything is fine, really.
Yes. I can do it.
I came here so as not to forget
why did we meet?
Translated and voiced by the studio
"Mobile TV"
commissioned by the online cinema Ivy
in 2024.